Guide to the Albert Ellis papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series V: Audio Visual Material, 1953-2007
  - Subseries V.2: Reel to Reel Audio, 1953-1975
    - Plastic base ¼ in x 1200 ft.
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 10)
        (Side 1: Mike Wallace, 1959 April 8. Chastity, WABD, "Probe," Fred Weiss, Fried, M., H. Whitman, 1958 January 22. Religion and Psychiatry, 1958 March 9. Homosexuality, 1958 January. Side 2: Creativity and Deviation, 1958 November. NBC TV Workshop Live, 1955 August. Martha Deane: How to Live with a Neurotic, 1957 October )
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 10)
        (AAP Tape Library. Vol. 21. Multiple Therapy with a Couple. Drs. Whitaker, Felder, Undated)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 10)
        (AAP Tape Library. Vol. 39. Congruent Therapy. Dr. Johnson, Undated)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 10)
        (Side 1: AE, Hidden Problems of Sex and Violence. Cooper Union Forum, 1960 November 30. Side 2: Mike Wallace interview, Undated)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 10)
        (Long John Radio Show. WOR. Reason and Emotion in Psychotherapy. First part. 1963 April 20)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 10)
        (Dr. E. Part III. Cross Country Check-up. 1965 November 12)(Note: See also Box 10 Folder 16, Box 206 Folder 5, Box 38 Folder 3)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 10)
        (Dr. E. Cross Country Check-up. Part IV. 1965 November 12)(Note: See also Box 10 Folder 15, Box 206 Folder 5, Box 38 Folder 3)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 206)
        (Workshop. Psychological Association Western NY. Orig. Buffalo. 1966 December 17)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 206)
        (Radio and TV interviews. Mike Wallace: Sex Without Guilt, 1959 April 8. Albert V. Freeman: SWG and Rational Therapy, 1959 July. Martha Deane: How to Live with a Neurotic, 1957 October. Creativity and Deviation, 1958 November. NBC TV Workshop: Love, 1955 August )
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 206)
        (Dr. Meyer Maskin and Dr. AE, 1963 November )
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 206)
        (Inter. With Sandra Mosely. Radio. 1964 April )
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 206)
        (Dr. E. Cross Country Check-Up. Part II. 1965 November 12)(Note: See also Box 10 Folder 15 and 16, Box 38 Folder 3)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 206)
        (Workshop. Washington. 1966 April 3)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 206)
        (Ethics and Psychology of Sex. Nathaniel Branden. San Antonio Towne, Undated)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 206)
        (AE on Kaleidoscope-Battle of the Doctors; 1961 August 3. Nudist #2 copy. Other side-AE on the Pat Michael Show, part 1; 1961 July 8)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 206)
        (AAP Tape Library. An SCEH Tape (Amer. Academy of Psychotherapists and the Society for Clinical and Experimental Hypnosis) (Vol. 59. Tape 1 of 2, Tape 2 of 2. Hypnosis for Students. Dr. Rothman, Undated)(2 folders)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 206)
        (AE-Tape #1. "Rational Emotive Psychotherapy." Esalen-Big Sur. Talk on RET and problems of self-worth. 1966 June )(Note: See also Box 206 Folder 12, 13.)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 206)
        (AE-Tape #2. "Rational Emotive Psychotherapy." Esalen-Big Sur. Interviewing people with problems. 1966 June )(Note: See also Box 206 Folder 11, 13.)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 206)
        (AE-Tape #3. "Rational Emotive Psychotherapy." Esalen-Big Sur. Living Rationally in These Times of Sex Revolution. 1966 June) (Note: See also Box 206 Folder 11, 12)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 206)
        (Rational Training 4. 1968 February 13)(Note: See also Box 205 Folder 5, Box 8 folders 10 and 13, Box 204 folder 8.)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 206)
        (RET Workshop Pittsburg, Kans. 2. Second day. 1970 August )
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 206)
        (AAP Institute-Airlee House, Warrenton, PA. AE-group leader. Jackie Clements. Stanley Klein. George Lott. Natalie Mann. Barry Sherman. Christine Sears. 1967 November 10)(Note: this is actually Airlie House in Warrenton VA, per the AAP’s list of past meetings)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 206)
        (1. LAMMI, PEDCE, LLARI, CAJST, MLUBE, 1966 October 28; 2. MLUBE, RUBRO, ETSSI, ROTSO, REFJA, 1966 November 2; 3. ANKBI, ETSAL, ERCSA, YERCA, ROTSO, 1966 October 30; 4. LEGDA, LISDA, IAGMA, LISDE, EIFPE, SORIR, 1966 October 30)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 7)
        (Dallas workshop-IWST Advanced Study in Rational Psychotherapy. With Dr. AE, Dr. Barry Brown, Mrs. Mary (Brownie) Wright, and Larry Hill. Side 1-recordings and comments. Side 2-therapy sessions. 1. Dr. AE with Barbara…. 2. Dr. Barry Brown with Vicki…. 3. Larry Hill with a woman…. .1969 December 6)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 7)
        (IRL Workshop-Houston, TX. 1968 December 7)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 7)
        (Exec. Workshop, 1970 April 28)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 7)
        (Dr. AE. Philadelphia-R.T. wksp. 1964 April 18)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 7)
        (Psychological Forums presents a debate. Does Psychoanalysis Do More Harm Than Good Dr AE and Dr. Harold Greenwald. Introduced by Lucy Freeman. Moderator: Dr. Emanuel Hammer. The Palm Gardens, NYC. Question and Answer period side 2. Original tape. 1964 May 1)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 7)
        (AE: Esalen Seminar. 1 to 4 of 4. 1968 August) (4 folders)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 7)
        (1. ALGHO, RLKJU, IEWSA, ELKGE, LISDE, NILLA,1966 October 22; 2. REJDA, OOCBE, CIRDA, EILES, 1966 October 26; 3. SORJO, GOLZO, EIFPE, AHSES, RUBBO, CCMTO, 1966 October 25; 4. ETSAL, YERCA, SURLO, LEMEL, SAWRI, 1966 October 24. Tucson, Ariz)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 7)
        (1. DAMDO, AHSCA, ANKWI, AHSES, 1966 October 18; 2. REVDA, PEDCE, LLARI, TAKAR, CAJPA, DAMDO, 1966 October 22; 3. SAWRI, DCMJI, VELNO, AHSES, BURLY, 1960 October 20; 4. ETSSI, LOFJA, TAWDO, CCMTO, 1966 October 19. Philadelphia PA. S. City)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 7)
        (1. ZAMAL, EROJO, IADRO, PIDCE, FLAFR, 1966 December 2; 2. ALGHO, GUPLO, IADRO, EAGBO, LOCCA, Undated; 3. IEWSA, DAMDO, SACAL, MOGJO, EIFPE, PAKJA, SIRAR, 1966 December 6, 7; 4.NIFCA, REBEL, LAPLY, HODMA, MISJO, DHJDO, 1966 December 5)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 7)
        (1. JUPRO, SEWRO, REKJU, VEDMI, RASRO, 1967 August 11; 2. DYHED, CEBMA, GIRDU, ERTLA, RASRO, EOLJO, SEWRO, 1967 September 6; 3. DAMDO, FFOES, ENOTO, NIFAR, NIFCA, EIFRI, 1967 September 1; 4. REDAR, CEBMA, REDAR, SITJA, NASBA, EACSH, LATAN, 1967 August 31)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 7)
        (1. LABJO, VELMO, HCSNA, SAWJO, NASBA, SITMA, NIWGE, NIWGE, HCSRO, RUBAL,1967 September 6, 7, 8, 9; 2. Interview with Dieter Steiner, Stern Magazine, AIPAN, EOLJO, EEMED, CAMAR, ETSSI, AIPAN, FALJU, MORRI, MAKIR, ILERO, REFCA, 1967 September 20, 21, 22; 3. ROKED, RUGST, POKLO, LODMA, LOGPH, ETSCH, KCMAN, LAKDE, GORCA, HCSLE, 1967 September 13, 14, 15; 4. ROGCA, URCBR, ARCNI, YARWA, FALJU, EIFRI, ZAYMA, EROJO, NIFMA, CUTTE, RATRO, ROMBI, CAMAR, 1967 September 9, 11)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 7)
        (1. HOCGE, WDEDO, MIDBE, ROGCA, LESLE, EEMED, FALJU, YATFL, EROJO, CEBSH, 1967 September 30, October 2; 2. EIFRI, DAPTO, UCSJO, OOBCH, REBJE, IEWIR, RAASI, Undated; 3. EEMJU, AEWHA, ELCBE, EAHAD, NOWSH, 1967 October 9; 4. POKLO, ILERO, GORSU, JCSJO, Undated)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 7)
        (1. OTSVA, ERFLO, NOMGE, 1968 May 2, 11; [2] Fri group, 1968 May 17; 3. Sat group, MCMJO, 1968 May 4; 4. OOKBA, PORRI, NEBLO, 1968 May 2)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 7)
        (Ellis/Greenwald debate. Copy for Dr. E, Undated)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 205)
        (Dr. AE. 1. Interview with depressed patient. 2. Theory and practice of Rational-emotive psychotherapy. Nebraska Psychiatric Inst. 1967 March)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 205)
        (AE. Presented: Illinois Unit, American Society of Dentistry for Children. Continental Plaza, Chicago IL. 1. AM session. 4. AM session concluded and PM session. 3. PM session concluded. 1966 November 9)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 205)
        (IRL Workshop. First tape, 2 sides. Starts at about 60. Probably erased by mistake a little at the beginning of the first side. 1964 June 12)(Note: See also Box 205 Folder 4.)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 205)
        (Second tape of IRL Workshop. Both sides. 1964 June 14)(Note: See also Box 205 Folder 3)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 205)
        (Rational Training Inst. 5. 1968 February 20)(Note: See also Box 206 Folder 14, Box 8 folders 10 and 13, Box 204 folder 8.)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 205)
        (Confidential material: for professional use only. 4 sessions, Workshops in Problems of Daily Living. 1966 October 28, November 4, 11, 18)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 205)
        (Bruce workshop. 1966 January 7)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 205)
        (San Francisco Rational Emotive Workshop. Side 1-Morning session to coffee break. Side 2-morning discussion. Drs. AE, Stewart Bedford, Barry Brown. 1 of 2. 1970 May 11)(Note: see also Box 205 Folder 9)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 205)
        (San Francisco Rational Emotive Workshop. Side 1-Afternoon live interviews. Side 2-Afternoon live interviews. Drs. AE, Stewart Bedford, Barry Brown. 2 of 2. 1970 May 11)(Note: See also Box 205 Folder 8)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 205)
        (LA Tapes. Side 1. J.W, Undated)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 205)
        (AE Workshop. Disneyland Hotel. 1963 May 5)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 205)
        (AE Speech and Questions and Discussion. Institute of Therapeutic Psychology, 205 W 20 St, Santa Ana, CA. 1963 May 6)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 205)
        (Mendota State Hospital workshop, Tape 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 of 5. 1967 June 27, 28)(5 folders)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 8)
        (Dr. AE, Dr. Leonard Haber. "A Rational Approach to Business." An unedited copy of original recording…. The Smith Studio. 1969 November 19)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 8)
        (IASRP All-day Workshop. 1970 October 25)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 8)
        (KVW Radio. Contact. (Torn info sheet.)%ne Part #2. Erotic …volution. 1965 May 19, 20)(Note: See also Box 8 Folder 4.)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 8)
        (KVW Radio. Contact. Part #3. The Erotic Revolution. #7 Calta family welfare clients. 1965 May 19, 20)(Note: See also Box 8 Folder 3.)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 8)
        (1. LIMPA, SORSH, ERCME, ARTBE, EILJO, 1967 January 14; 2. NIGRU, SORJO, FUTRO, RBARO, SOMLI, EIFPE, 1967 January 18. 3. IEWEL, REKJU, NABLO, RAMRU, RABJE, TLERU, 1967 January 16; 4. ALBHE, REMEL, "[blank]", 1967 January 14)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 8)
        (1. RIJPA, DAMDO, LAPLY, REVLA, LIMAR, 1966 July 30; 2. REPAN, TORCA, HSAAL, HCSCH, SANBA, EOBKT, Undated; 3. ARGDI, CINBL, TIKRO, HCSLE, Undated; 4. EHSSH, ANKWI, BLADI, HOCFR, HOJMA, HCSFL, 1966 August 2. Hinesville)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 8)
        (TORSE, CAPAN [], LEKPO, 1968 June 29; LISMA, EERRO, 1968 July 1; ARKEL, EIBLY, EERJA,1968 July 3; WOLJO, ORBHO, ORBWI, 1968 July 3)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 8)
        (1. NIHEI, EABCO, WOLVO, HERAD, 1968 July 9; 2. ORBWI, LKSLY, RIKED, 1968 July 3; 3. ROSSH, EERRO, NIWIV, XEWMO, Undated; 4. LKSLY, LUSPE, OTSLO Undated)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 8)
        (IASRP Seminar, Dr. AE, 1970 May 13)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 8)
        (Rational Training Inst. 6. 1968 February 27)(Note: See also Box 205 folder 5, Box 206 folder 14, Box 8 folder 13, Box 204 folder 8.)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 8)
        (1. LKSLY, TAKAN, EERRO, 1968 June 27; 2. EIPRO, RAHLO, CINVI, 1968 June 28; 3. NIHWA, LOGAL, LENRO, Undated; 4. YAMTH, WOLJO, SOMMA, Undated)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 8)
        (1. NODJO, EIPRO, HCSAL, 1968 June 21; 2. BEWAR, RAMJA, SIWHE, YAMTH, 1968 June 27; 3. RAHLO, ETBLY, Undated; 4. KSAMA, LOCBA, MOLAN, Undated)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 8)
        (Rational Training Inst. 1 Dr. AE and Dr. Maxie Maultsby and 10 rational training group members. 1968 January 23)(Note: See also Box 205 folder 5, Box 206 folder 14, Box 8 folder 10, Box 204 folder 8)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 8)
        (Oakland Group-Lake Forest Academy discussion. AAP. 1959)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 8)
        (Can Man Be Sane in an Insane Society. SDUPI, Undated)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 8)
        (Dr. AE-UMD. Side 1: Discussion period with Elem. Sch. Counseling and Guidance Institute Participants. Side 2: Discussion continued. Convocation Address. "Psychotherapy in Sexual and Non-sexual Hangups." RET and Schl. Guidance. 1969 February 13)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 8)
        (Psyther in Action. WEVD. AE, Ruth Cohn, Gus Woltman. 1953 February 10)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 204)
        (AAP Workshop. AE. Side 1: Malone. Side 2: Ellis, 1957)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 204)
        (Hidden Probs Revised; 1960 November 30. Cooper Union. Birnbaum, etc, and Selma. 1961 May 6. Mannie, Birnbaum, Lee and Alex Levine continued.. 1961 May 6)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 204)
        (AE. Workshop. San Francisco. Bedford. 1966 June )
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 204)
        (Lecture by Dr. AE. Subj: "Rational Psycho-Therapy." Limitas of RT. 1961 March 22)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 204)
        (MORLI 3 NS Religion of Housework, 1957 June 29. 13 NS Worthwhileness, 1957 September 27. 19 NS Progress by Marital Partners, 1957 November 30. 28 Progress, 1958 April 9. Dupl)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 204)
        (AAP Tape Library. Vol. 58. Provocative Theory. Theory of Provocative Therapy. Mr. Farrelly, Undated)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 204)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 204)
        (Rational Training Inst. 3. 1968 February 6)(Note: See also Box 205 folder 5, Box 206 folder 14, Box 8 folders 10 and 13.)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 204)
        (Side 1: 0, no.1. 1st session. 38 yr old married salesman-temper tantrums, 1964. 1006 no. 2. 11th session. 37 yr old wife-borderline psychotic-guilt and self blame, 1964. Side 2: 0, no. 3. 1st session. 27 yr old husband-severe anxiety about dying, 1964. 1129-blank. John Williams, Seattle, Wash. Confidential Material)
        (Note: See also Box 204 folder 10)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 204)
        (Side 1: 0, no. 8. 44 yr old married male-drinking-temper-assault-need for approval, 1966. 1167 no. 12. 27 yr old husband-feels inadequate and hopeless-self blame-1st session, 1964. Side 2: 0, no. 13. 20 yr old student-feels worthless-anger-competitive, 1967. No. 14. 34 yr old divorced male-overcoming of blame and hostility-new attitudes in sex, 1967. John Williams, Seattle, Wash. Confidential Material)(Note: See also Box 204 folder 9)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 204)
        (AE-Seminar. Merrill-Palmer School. 1960 February 2)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 204)
        (Convo-Dr. E. Sex, Sanity and Psychotherapy, Macalester. Waves of muffle. Save morolitz. Written. 1965 January 28)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 204)
        (Sex, Identity, and the College Student, 1964 May. Irrational Man and Rational Psychotherapy, Univ. Minn, 1964 May 8. Talks, Orig)(Note: Includes notes and correspondence)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 204)
        (Dr. AE. Sill, LU Hall. EMU Eastern Mich. Univ.-Dub from audiotape. Rec. 1968 March 10)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 204)
        (D.G. Paterson Memorial Lecture by AE. "Irrational Man and Rational Psychotherapy." U of Minn. 1964 May 8)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 204)
        (Sex, Sanity, and Psychotherapy. Talk by Dr. AE, Beverly H.S. Auditorium. Introduced by Dr. Albert V. Freeman, Taped by KPFK, Los Angeles. 1964 September )(Note: No reel)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 9)
        (AAP Tape Library--Volume 1--Loretta. Drs. Ellis, Felder, Rogers, Undated)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 9)
        (AAP Tape Library--Volume 3--Mr. Vac. Dr. Rogers, Undated)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 9)
        (AAP Tape Library--Volume 7--Mike. Dr. Rogers, Undated)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 9)
        (AAP Tape Library--Volume 9--Part C. Composite Tape Recording. Dr. A Levitsky, Undated)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 9)
        (AAP Tape Library--Volume 11--John Jones. Dr. Ellis, Undated)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 9)
        (AAP Tape Library--Volume 14--Jim. Dr. Rosen, Undated)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 9)
        (AAP Tape Library--Volume 22--Interview with Theodor. Reik, Undated)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 9)
        (AAP Tape Library--Volume 30--Desensitization for Phobia. Dr. Wolpe, Undated)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 9)
        (AAP Tape Library--Volume 33--Laura. The Therapeutic Self. Dr. Watkins, Undated)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 9)
        (AAP Tape Library--Volume 42--Hypnotic LSD Trips. Dr. Greenwald, Undated)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 9)
        (AAP Tape Library--Volume 48--Four Psychotherapies. Drs. Murray, Ellis, Cautela, Seidenberg, Undated)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 9)
        (AAP Tape Library--Volume 55--Vision and Personality. Dr. Guze, Undated)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 9)
        (For Professional Use: Samples from Six Therapists for AAP Research Project, Undated)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 9)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 9)
        (On the Treatment of Homosexuality. A tape recording of two one-and-one-half-hour therapeutic sessions with four male homosexuals, conducted by Nathaniel Branden. For professional use only, Undated)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 207)
        (The Case of Mrs. Schmidt by Joseph Wolpe, M.D, Undated)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 207)
        (E-Telephone Interview. Recorded by L. Douglas Fols, Dean of Students, Jamestown Community College, Jamestown NY. Springfield College Phone Interview. 1966 July 28)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 207)
        (Hyp Inductn, Undated)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 207)
        (Hyp Techs. 1963)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 207)
        (Sex, Identity, and the College Student. U. of Wisconsin YMCA. From Probasco, YMCA, Madison, Wisc, Undated)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 207)
        (1. IEWAL, BLAJA, YAMJA, VADJA, HCSCH, 1966 July 20; [no 2]; 3. PIFCO, ULBJU, DAPTO, UEKMA, ATSFA, BORLI, EHSSH, PIFCO, EOBIK, KCEMA, ERTLA, UAPCA, 1966 July 21; 4. RAWDO, OHRRO, SAMPA, HCSDO, ATSFA, 1966 July 19)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 207)
        (1. ETSCH, MOGMA, UHWDE, IEWJO, SARJU, RUTLA, 1966 September 19; 2. RUTRI, SAWRI, EPSJO, EIWBA, MIZKA, GOLLO, 1966 September 27; Karen Silver, RHEDO, NEHDE, ANKBI, ULBHO, 1966 September 27; 4. ARGBI, WELLI, RAWDO, EPSJO, BABFA, YOBGE, ARTBE, 1966 September 23. Lancaster PA)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 207)
        (1. RAMVI, LAGEV, ROCLU, CELRO, 1968 June 7; 2. IESSA, LIWNO, RPSJO, Fri eve, Undated; 3. RPSJO, ARKSO, REBAD, 1968 June 8; 4. ORGMA, BARRI, SAYST, Undated)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 207)
        (1. RUTMA, DNARO, 1968 May 29; 2. REHRI, IEWIR, LOHRO, Undated; 3. DAMDO, NOFBO, OHSJU, 1968 May 31; 4. DUJDO, IADMA, OLSJA, Undated)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 207)
        (Marathon-opening session, 1968 June 1; 2. LIWBA, ROCMI, DNARO, 1968 June 5; 3. IESDA, LOHRO,, Undated; 4. ORGMA, RNERA, REBAD, 1968 June 3)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 207)
        (1. HESBA, SIWHE, TORAM, 1968 June 19; BAGKE, WOLJO, 1968 June 21; 3. SACST, FOHJA, LOHSA, Undated; 4. CAREL, OLBLE, ERGTA, 1968 June 20)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 207)
        (1. RPSJO, WOLJO, ORGMA, 1968 June 14; 2. Wednesday group, Undated; 3. KSAFR, YEMJO, 1968 June 19; 4. Monday group, RPSJO, Undated)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 207)
        (1. BATDA, LAGCA, SALAL, EHSSH, SIRMI, TIMKE, 1966 July 23; 2. ULBJO, ROBKI, RAKMA, Undated; 3. SANBA, BORLI, LATDEDOWLO, 1966 July 27; 4. HSAAL, DAMDO, NABLO, LISNO, SAMPA, 1966 July 28. Louisville, KY)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 207)
        (1. EOBKI, FOHGA, RAKMA, LLARI, 1966 July 15; 2. LIGEV, PIFCO, 1966 July 18; 3. ERTDO, PIFCO, IEWLI, RIMCA, GUHBA, 1966 July 16, 18; 4. MASNA, GESBL, LAGCA, EHSSH, 1966 July 16. Grand Rapids, Mich, Beltline)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 207)
        (Psychology for Today, radio broadcast made at Fort Dodge workshop. Dr. AE is interviewed by Dr. Marianne McManus about Rational Emotive Therapy and rational thinking. Broadcast over W.O.I. 1972 May )
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 207)
        (Dr. AE, interview on Rational Living with Mrs. Sidney [Bert] S. Smith. Hogg Foundation, Texas. The Human Condition. 1974 March)(Note: Includes recording notes.)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 207)
        (Abreactv [] sessn with Anon Patient and Therapist, Undated)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 207)
        (Idear []. AE inter with D. McPherson. CBC Radio. Just a Minute No. 93. 1973 August )
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 13)
        (1. EIFAB, BEWAR, RIBJO, EROJO, NAVDA, REPTH, DAMDO, 1967 August 4; 2. OOGRB, CAMSP, ATSJA, BURCH, HEMGE, RASRO, CCMED, VELCE, 1967 August 9; 3. PITGU, SAWRI, BURFL, RIBJO, BIRMA, 1967 August 7; CABBE, RIFAB, DAMDO, MANEL, OOGRD, EOLJO, 1967 August 5, 7. N. Oxford, Mass)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 13)
        (1. RUBRO, ROBAI, ELKRA, ARGBI, HOCGE, 1967 June 29, 30; 2. RONGE, ROBAI, LEBSA, VADJA, CABBE, HAKRO, 1967 July 5; 3. NAVTR, MOCRO, TIHDO, SORMA, 1967 June 30, July 3, 5; 4. NILJO, REGPA, ARFJA, RUMJE, MOCRO, 1967 June 30)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 13)
        (1. JUPRO, CAMSP, CEMEM, LISJO, RUGST, 1967 August 15; EOLJO, UUPBO, CAMSP, ERBEW, ORGFR, RUGST, 1967 August 22; [3] NONMA, REHMA, LEFLA, CEBMA, MIZCA, ORGFR, NYLRO, 1967 August 23, 24; LEWRO, MANMI, RUCJA, DYHED, AEPBO, LEWRO, GUPLU, 1967 August 16, 17)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 13)
        (1. YEMJU, ARKSU, OLBLO, 1968 May 11; 2. LEKPO, OLSJA, LEDDA, 1968 May 17; 3. NIWVI, LOCBA, TAKHO, 1968 May 14; 4. ODEKA, Mon. 7:15 group, Undated. Bill Vaughan Original)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 13)
        (1. REPTH, AIDMA, CABBE, DAMDO, GISMA, 1967 July 22; 2. BEWAR, SAWEL, LEBBE, REGPA, NILJA, EITAN, 1967 July 21; 3. AEPBO, CALCH, SOYDA, NERMO, SAMAR, Undated; 4. LAHSH, AHCBE, WOLJO, NUJHE, LISHO, 1967 July 22, 24)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 13)
        (1. Monday 7:15 grp, TEPAL, 1968 May 6, 7; 2. LEDDA, DAMDO, TORJU, 1968 May 10; 3. WLEBE, ORBHO, NIWVI, 1968 May 8; IRDJO, NEMWI, Wed group Undated. T.A.M. 45)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 13)
        (1. BAHIR, OLBGE, ARBMA, 1968 September 7; HCSJA, ERGCA, 1968 September 10; 3. NILBA, LAWKA, REHNE, Undated; 4. LEFRU, ORBRO, CORAN, 1968 September 9)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 13)
        (ATSJA, REGGR, OLSDO, BURFL, RIFSH, 1967 August 3; SEWEV, ARGBI, HACMA, OOGRO, TIDDO, REPBO, 1967 August 1; LEKGE, BURCH, SEWRO, MANMI, SXZJO, 1967 August 2; PETMA, DAMDO, POKLO, REVMA, OOGLE, EOLJO, 1967 July 31. Columbia, SC)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 13)
        (1. BEWAR, MISAL, ETSJO, SYZJO, TIDDO, 1967 July 25; OOHMA, ETSJO, BEWAR, REPET, 1967 July 28; NILRO, Raymond Corsini, NOVHO, AHCBE, NIFCA, 1967 July 29; 4. ETSJO, CAMSP, AEPBO, YOBGE, OOHMA, Fri group, 1967 July 28. Houston, Tex., Irvington)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 13)
        (1. HESSO, RUBBO, ROBAI, LIWMO, TIDDO, 1967 July 11; 2. MAUTR [], NAVDA, TLAIR, GISMA, EPSBA, GUPLU, TALHE, 1967 July 14, 17; 3. CAMSP, DUJDO, LOHCH, LIWMO, CAMSP, MCMHO, 1967 July 13, 14; 4. RACBE, BUDBI, REGRO, REGRO, ERGMA, 1967 July 12, 13. Calif)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 13)
        (1. LAHRI, TIDDO, OHTMI, NALNO, YOBSA, LAHRI, Undated; 2. REGBL, SAWRI, blank, Tues nite group, Undated; 3. LETCE, EROJO, EIFDO, RACBE, EIVIL, 1967 July 10; 4. REFPE, NAVTR, NAVDA, LOHCH, SEWRO, 1967 July 8. Longview, Tex)
      - Reel to Reel Audio: (Box 13)